<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soccer on Peyton Thomas</title>
    <link>/tags/soccer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soccer on Peyton Thomas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/soccer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where Expected Goals Falls Short</title>
      <link>/2021/04/20/where-expected-goals-falls-short/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/20/where-expected-goals-falls-short/</guid>
      <description>Recently across the soccer world. Fans have been accustomed to an “Expected Goals(xG)” metric attached to each team which represents how many goals that team should be expected to score over the course of the game. The metric has been created by assigning each shot a team takes a value on a scale from 0 to 1 based on how likely that shot would be a goal. The factors included in each shot includes the distance, position of defenders, type and speed of pass, type of shot, shot angles and other aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is The Dirtiest Player In The History of MLS?</title>
      <link>/2021/03/30/who-is-the-dirtiest-player-in-the-history-of-mls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/03/30/who-is-the-dirtiest-player-in-the-history-of-mls/</guid>
      <description>Following the 1994 FIFA World Cup, the U.S Soccer Federation decided it was the right time to create a Division 1 soccer league within the country. Starting play in 1996 with 10 teams, Major League Soccer has now completed 25 seasons and expanded to a whopping 27 clubs, with plans out to 30 by the 2023 season.
Throughout that history, the league has seen a number of aggressive, tough, and physical players pass through the ranks, coming from different countries across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
